There's nothing quite like ice hockey!
Yeah.
Let's go next week!
But nearly everyone there is a stranger.
I'm not sure I want to.
Huh? You won't go?
I haven't decided.
I'll be bored all alone.
The other girls will be there.
They said they'd be back next week.
Nao, do you have plans next Sunday?
Well...
You're just gonna read manga.
And that's fine, but outdoors is outdoors!
Just so you know, the hockey rink
is inside. If anything, it's indoors.
You know what I mean.
What is it?
Look!
Take you back?
Why do you have such an
old photo on your phone?
My dad scanned it for me.
You were so cute, Nao. My dad always
said you had a knack for ice hockey.
While I appreciate you carrying
that photo everywhere,
my heart was set on figure
skating, so I switched.
But since I was no good at spin
jumps, I quit skating, too.
No, that's not the point
I'm trying to make.
It's not like jumping
is useful in ice hockey.
Why are you pushing me to play so much?
Well, although I can't deny that playing
hockey again felt nostalgic and fun,
I mostly just wanna do
something with you again.
Ready? Here it comes, Nao!
Okay!
Nice, Nao!
Y-Yeah!
So? I'm begging you!
C'mon, I don't wanna go alone!
I'll treat you to whatever you want!
You'd do that for me?
Yup! How does a Monkey Complete sound?
All right.
Heck yeah!
But don't think the Monkey
will work next time.
Nice! I hooked her!
I see!
Is that an ice hockey book?
Yup!
You're into it.
Mmm!
Hey, get your hands moving!
Oops, sorry!
No, I was talking to Sis.
But you've made good progress,
so you're allowed a break.
I just wanted to brush up
before the next trial class!
Where's it from?
I saw it in the library!
So you snatched it?
Yup! Next class, I think
we'll be training for speed!
Lemme see!
Still, those stretches we did
felt awfully like dancing.
True.
Well, actually... It might
come in handy for this!
I wonder...
Break's over! If we don't finish these,
we can't show 'em off!
Our president's the furthest behind!
Gulp!
It's hard to tell who's president, right?
Ma?
Hmm? Yeah.
Oh, yeah! The TV show I was talking
about is coming this weekend!
Really?!
And from Tokyo!
Ooh!
Thanks for having us.
Of course. We're glad that you came.
It's a program about the ryokan and
Kinugawa's charms and specialties!
They took Grandma's suggestion and
are doing a bit about our family farm!
Nice!
How about Mami's family?
Huh? My dad's just a salaryman.
But your papa is cool!
Yeah, yeah!
By the way, what's in those bags?
Manaka, Ayaka. Get ready.
Okay!
All right! Let's get started.
Here we have the senior
hostess of Shikiootoro.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
And this is the future hostess.
Lastly, the beautiful, next-gen sisters.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
And... their friends.
Huh? Why are you here?
And in those outfits...
Can we get "Team Next-Gen" and their
friends to show us around the ryokan?
Sure!
These are from my family's Yanagida Farms.
We pride ourselves on our sweet
and juicy strawberries!
Eat just one and you'll
see what she means!
A little bit of condensed milk
makes them all the more sweet!
But it's best to eat 'em plain,
straight from nature!
Thanks for helping! You guys made it easy!
Actually, we're filming again tomorrow.
Think you could help?
Tomorrow? Oh, dear me!
I've got important plans tomorrow!
Acting like a famous actress, are we?
Important plans?
Tomorrow, we're going to
an ice hockey trial class.
Ice hockey trial class?
What? Are you serious?!
Yes, of course! With pleasure!
Yes! Have a good day!
Hell yeah!
Talk about happy.
What was that call about?
Tomorrow, a TV show from Tokyo is coming!
Eh?!
They wanna cover our trial class!
And? You agreed to it?
Of course, my horse!
Without even asking me?
Don't worry, I'm great at PR!
Ah! What to wear tomorrow?!
Maybe I should get my hair done!
Well, you know they're not coming
to cover you, but the class, right?
I'm so excited!
Nao! Good morning!
Coming in!
Morning, Riko. You're the best.
No way! You're the best!
Nao! Knock-knock.
Coming in! Okay! Kachak.
I knew you'd be asleep.
What now?
Don't "What now?" me. You promised.
Gimme a break.
Monkey...
...Complete.
All right, already.
Cute pajamas!
C'mon, now! Let's get you ready!
H-Hey! I can change on my own!
Good morning!
Good morning.
She looks nothing like last time.
It's scary.
Thanks to you guys,
we'll be on TV! Thanks!
Oh, it was nothing!
TV?
For a Tokyo variety program!
Yeah?
Can I go home?
Now, now.
Well, go change into your jerseys.
You know where, right?
Yeah!
Brr! It's like Alaska in here!
Not that I've been there.
Sorry to keep you!
No, it's fine!
Use this if you like.
Ooh, thanks!
Still, I'm shocked you've got
such a beautiful stadium.
Thank you!
Nikko Dream Monkeys
is a pro ice hockey team.
They were founded in 1925.
It's been supported by both fans
and businesses over its many years.
It's that old, huh?
Our team color represents our love
of the community and their love for us.
In fact, the team has many
players who grew up here.
This class is us giving back.
We thought it would be a good
way to engage with the kids.
We hope that they'll enjoy ice hockey,
become interested, and join the team.
And while that's our goal,
even if they don't,
we hope that they experience
the thrill of hockey.
We really do.
Yoko's actually serious today.
I read that profile of yours.
Yeah?
When did she give them that?
You played hockey yourself, Matsunaga?
And represented Japan?
Oh, you saw that part?!
Believe it or not, I was incredible!
Yeah...
Argh. She's back to normal.
I was born here in Nikko.
I played hockey when I was little,
and have loved it ever since!
Yes! I'm single and available!
Quit it, Yoko!
Good! Everyone ready?
Yeah!
Let's start with stretches.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Two, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, good!
--They're all having fun.
--Three, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
--Seems so.
--Three, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
--I'm totally killing it!
--Three, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
--What an evil face, Yoko.
--Four, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight!
--Yup! I can feel my arms stretching out!
--Four, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight!
Next is side-walk. Go!
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
--Two, two, three, four,
--This is totally a dance.
five, six, seven, eight.
--It sure is.
--Three, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
--Ice hockey stretches sure are odd.
--Three, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
--Yeah, well...
--Four, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
--Five, two, three, four, five, six...
--Quit with that face.
What are they practicing?
Edge control. It's important to
master balance when skating.
Takagi, you're good at skating!
Next is passing practice!
Kao!
Yup!
Ma!
Right!
Here!
Got it!
Mana!
Yup!
Saginuma! Here it comes!
Okay!
I'll be careful today.
Oof! Whoa! I'm sorry!
Wow!
Nao!
Okay.
Riko Saginuma, was it? Where have I...?
So, any plans for the future?
R-Right!
I hope to increase the
popularity of ice hockey.
It's very much a minor sport in Japan,
but ice hockey is truly fascinating!
I want everyone out there
to see for themselves!
You're right. After coming here today,
it does seem pretty interesting.
Really? Then you should
definitely go see a match!
I will.
There's the teamwork, the speed...
The puck movement on the rink
is something you just have to see.
Even the girls get fierce and competitive.
The way they fight and steal
the puck--it's an intense sport!
Oh?
I guarantee if you watch just once,
you'll see how interesting it is.
Someday, we'll pack this entire arena
with fans. That's the dream I believe in.
Well, I hope your dream comes true.
Everyone, gather up!
Okay!
We'll be challenging you
in a new way today.
It's time to get comfortable with one
of hockey's best highlights--its speed.
I knew it!
Skate as fast as you can towards
the goal, touch the line, and return.
Okay!
Whoa! We went so fast!
Yeah! Faster than I thought!
Faster than a car!
I sincerely doubt it.
Takagi skates so gracefully!
I know!
You okay?
Yeah.
Riko Saginuma...
Oh! Is your father one of our
old players, Kenji Saginuma?
Yeah, that's right.
Tell me that sooner! Is he doing well?
Yup! He's coaching at a college in Tokyo!
That's good to hear! So, what do you think?!
Will you guys come back next week?!
Yeah!
Is "okey-dokey" not gonna happen?
Just be glad.
--Saginuma!
--Hmm?
Thanks for earlier!
Oh, no problem!
It was so cool how you slid
right in and caught Ayaka!
Yeah. And how you stopped
Sis' terrible passes.
You're sisters?
That's right.
I'm so sorry about my wreck of a sister.
Don't call me a wreck!
Your little sister's mature.
Yeah, she is.
Who's the big sis now?
Not you guys, too!
Saginuma, you've played hockey before?
Yeah! Ever since I was little... with Nao!
Wha--?!
Our coach seemed to know your dad.
Yup! He played for the Dream Monkeys!
You're a thoroughbred!
But after Nao switched to figure skating,
it was boring by myself.
That's not--!
Figure skating?! Wow!
That's why you're so elegant!
Uh...
You skate so gracefully!
Yeah! Like nobility!
Wha--?
You know it! She's like
a swan on the ice! Glide!
By the way, you're all from Kinugawa?
Uh-huh! My house is a ryokan!
Really?
You should come sometime!
Can I?!
Of course!
This is nuts.
What is?
All these cute girls
coming to the trial class...
Saginuma's daughter being one of them...
That TV show coming to film...
Could the goddess of luck
be smiling upon me?!
It's true that good things are happening,
but don't get too excited.
The good life rarely lasts.
I can overcome whatever
misfortunes come my way!
Come on, unhappy!
I somewhat envy your positive attitude,
but it does get annoying.
Thanks, all. You were a great help today.
Thank you, too!
I'll let you know when the program airs.
Thanks! We can't wait!
See you.
Oh. Ice hockey...
Hmm? Yeah?
You guys look pretty
good at it. Keep it up.
Right!
--See you!
--Bye!
Coming next week?
--Yup!
--Eh?!
That was fun today!
Yeah!
Even more than last week!
Saginuma and Takagi seem like nice people!
Takagi's a bit shy, though.
For ice hockey, you need
six people to play, right?
Yup.
Since there're six of us who come,
couldn't we form a team?!
We could!
Or maybe we can join Dream Monkeys!
Let's talk to 'em next week!
Good idea!
I bet those two will be up for it!
Yeah.
Mami? Something wrong?
No, I'm looking forward to it.
I see!
Hey, Mami?
Hi, Manaka. Got a minute?
Yeah. I'm just reviewing
what we did today.
Feels weird! If only studying
for school was this easy!
I see.
Mami?
I'm sorry.
Huh?
I... can't join the team.
Huh? Why not?
Um, because after the second
semester, I'm transferring schools.
Huh?
You can't do this anymore?
What's that mean?
Exactly how it sounds.
Taste the best there is,
right here in Japan!