Manaka!
Yo!
We're finally back at it today!
Yup!
No more exams!
And we're in the same school!
We sure are!
I feel left out and I don't like it.
Ugh! I wish I was a high schooler!
Now, now. Cheer up, new club president.
You're president?
Yup! I was the only one left,
so I recruited eight of my friends!
Clever girl.
This year, I'm giving embroidery
and hockey all I've got!
Pumped up, are we?
Manaka! Kaoruko! Yay!
Riko!
Hey! Practice this weekend?
Okey-dokey!
Kaorun, did you turn into Yoko?
Wanna come over after practice?
Yeah! Totally!
Would you guys like to join
Nikko Dream Monkeys?
Huh?
You mean...?
As in becoming official members.
You got a taste of hockey, and we can't
extend the trial class forever.
Team members, huh?
I've been wanting to ask
ever since the match.
Since you're in high school now,
it's about time I did.
Yoko's been itching to bring
it up for the longest time.
But finally, the time has come!
Actually, we've been talking
about what to do, too.
Sure, we might have lost
Mami's send-off match,
but we got to experience
how exciting ice hockey is,
and getting to put what we learned
into practice was an amazing feeling.
How do we join the team?
Are you guys telling me that you enjoy
ice hockey? That you wanna keep at it?
Yeah.
Huh?! Real tears?!
I'm not crying! I'm not!
You're crying, clear as day!
I hear your enthusiasm, loud and clear!
So, we can join, right?
Yes! If you pass the tests.
Tests?
Written and skills.
Eh? A written test? I've gotta
study for hockey, too?
Of course!
The world isn't kind, is it?
The skills test is skating and
100 laps around the rink.
The written test covers the rules.
Yu?
It shouldn't have gone like that.
Huh? But we won the match.
You think that matters? It's a given
we'll win, but what matters is how!
Kuga and Sachin,
your coordination was awful.
There's nothing to be happy about.
We're champs, but only in Japan!
We're nothing on the world stage!
Even so...
Just 'cuz you're a U-16 MVP...
What have I said that's wrong?
What you've said is true. But that
doesn't mean it helps to be said.
So pointing out our weak
points doesn't help?!
It helps, but ice hockey is a team sport.
You don't think I know?! But you can't be
a good team without individual skill!
Teams that make up for
shortcomings are the worst!
Yu...
What's wrong?
Yu!
I quit. I'm sick of hockey
and this team.
And you were just picked as MVP, too...
Why not take a break and come back?
I won't come back. I'm leaving Kushiro.
What?
I'm staying with my grandparents in Nikko.
I'll find a school there.
In Nikko... I see...
I won't stop you from leaving the team,
but don't give up hockey.
Hopefully, we'll see you
in the rink again.
I already made up my mind.
Yu! Could you lend me
a hand making donuts?
Okay.
Grandma, are these done?
A bit longer. They're better overcooked.
Oh, really? They smell delicious.
Can't contact her?
She's not picking up.
So, why did Yu Kiyose come to Nikko?
Some squabble with her teammates.
She left Snow White and Kushiro behind
to live here with her grandparents.
I see.
Snow White's coach, Atsumi Kawakami,
used to be my teammate.
She wants me to do something.
If she's the U-16 MVP ace of
a strong team, she must be good.
She really is.
If Yu Kiyose quits for good, it's a huge
loss for ice hockey in Japan.
You must think really highly of her.
A girl knowing nothing but hockey runs off
to start a new life as a normal girl...
Little does she know she's
fallen straight into my claws!
Quit with that face. It's scary.
The Dream Monkeys play in the Women's
Ice Hockey All-Japan Championship B.
Unfortunately, we've lost
in the first match every year.
On the other hand, Snow White
fell to B last season,
but they used to be a top contender
in A where the best eight teams play.
Why'd they fall to B?
'Cuz they lost Yu Kiyose.
If their ace comes to us,
we can win in B and rank up to A!
This is a once-in-a-lifetime chance!
There it is. I knew you
were up to something.
You won't get away, Yu Kiyose!
Argh! I like hockey, but studying sucks!
I'll just remember the rules with my body!
Using your leg to obstruct
a player is called "kneeing."
Sis! I'm coming in!
Hmm? What are you doing?
Studying rules. Stuff doesn't
stick in my head when I read.
It's way easier to remember
when I use my body!
Need help studying?
Huh, really?! Ayaka, ask me questions!
Question one: How much
time-out for a minor penalty?
Um...
Give up? The answer's two minutes.
Question two: What's tripping?
Tripping?
Making the opponent fall over.
Question three: What causes
a five-minute penalty?
Oh, I know! Magi!
No, not "magician."
I meant, "majority"!
Bzzt! A "major penalty."
Yeah, that! Almost had it!
Not even close.
Next question: What is "butt ending"?
Huh? When the main character dies?
That's "bad ending"! It's when you
jab people with the handle!
You're totally hopeless!
Well, it's hard!
I don't think it's that hard.
How about easy ones?
Yes, please!
Using your hand or stick
to stop a player is...?
I know! Holding!
Correct!
Woo-hoo! Hmm?
Ayaka, you know the rules?
You're not using a book.
Of course!
Whoa!
At this rate, you're not gonna pass, Sis.
Wha--?! Oh no!
Too slow! Speed it up!
Your stamina's much better, Manaka.
Yeah! I've been running
and working out every day!
Good, good!
Something wrong, Aya?
No, I'm fine.
Okay! Break's over!
Right!
Naomi! Slow start!
Riko! Keep your speed up!
Manaka! You can do better!
Kaoruko! Finish stronger!
Ayaka...!
Don't you think Yoko's getting harsher?
Agreed. It's her "tough love."
If she's going for a carrot
and stick approach,
I'd like more carrot and less stick.
I'm with you!
What is our "carrot"?
Everyone passing the test?
That'd be nice!
Aya?
I think I might not pass.
Huh? What are you talking about?
Compared to you guys,
I have no endurance and I'm slow.
I still can't get used
to wearing the gear.
I can't even move how I want.
Ayaka...
Oh, well! I might be the only one
who fails, but whatever!
Hey, what are you saying?
We're playing together!
Well, I want to.
Then...!
But if I can't, I can't.
There's no point unless
we're all together.
Kao...
It's either all of us, or none of us.
I think so, too.
Riko...
Same. You're small and cute,
so we need you on the team.
What's that mean?
Mmm!
Let's all pass, together!
Right!
Let's do this!
Yeah!
--Sis!
--Hmm?
Can I come with you?
Sure, but I thought you were
afraid of ghosts at night.
I'm still scared, but...
Starting today, I'm running!
All right!
Today, we'll work on
endurance! Go do 50 laps!
Okay!
Aya, keep it up!
Yeah!
You've got this!
I know!
Aya!
Okay!
That's it. That's what's important.
What is?
One of them is too young and too small.
She can't do what the others can do.
She's probably flustered,
but she's not losing to it.
Individual skill is important,
but it's just as important
for a team to become one.
Those girls know that without being told.
By supporting one another,
they'll all become stronger.
Hey, Sato! Don't go
stealing the good lines!
Huh?
Thanks for today...
I'm pooped!
My legs feel like a baby fawn's.
I can't walk a single step!
Huh?
Hmm?
You're...?
Are you guys the tryouts?
Are you guys... our senpais?!
I just can't remember the rules!
What can I do to help?
Huh? Don't you have a rule book?
I do, but... Are there any tricks to it?
Good old memorization.
Go figure.
I'm way slower than everyone.
I just can't keep up with 'em.
The 100-lap test?
It's not a race, you know.
Really?
The whole point of it is
to learn efficient skating.
Yeah?
So just relax, find what works
for you, and skate till it's over.
Till it's over...
That's right. Panic too much
and your skating will be sloppy.
Right!
Good luck! I'm looking forward
to playing with you!
Yeah!
It's time.
Yup. I hope we pass.
I did everything I can. If Yoko fails me,
I'll cry till she gives in.
Eh? You'll cry?
Well, I really wanna pass!
Let's do it! All of us! And then
we'll play hockey together!
You bet!
All right. Time's up!
Everybody passed the written test.
Yay! Yippee!
It was crazy easy.
She's far too happy.
Next up is the skills test!
Right!
Lastly, the 100 laps. Good luck.
Thanks!
Ready?!
Go figure. I'm falling behind.
Anyway, just focus on
skating till it's over.
Ayaka, fight!
Aya!
Ayacchi!
Keep it up, Aya!
It's not just me. Everyone's suffering.
Keep it up!
Ayaka! Last lap!
It hurts! I can't do it!
Ayaka!
--Aya!
--Ayacchi!
You're so close!
Keep it up!
Fight!
Almost there!
They're waiting for me! I've gotta finish!
I'm skating my way till it's over!
Just a bit more!
Ready, set...
Goal!
I did it! I skated it!
They all crossed the finish
line together! Golly!
Thank goodness!
You did it!
We finished together!
Ayacchi, nice work!
Good job finishing!
Yoko!
Everyone passes! Congrats!
Woo-hoo!
Isn't that great?
Now then...
There's one last thing to do.
This number again? Sheesh.
Anyone home?!
A-A trespasser?
Blocking my number won't stop me.
Wh-Who are you?
The person whose calls
you've been ignoring!
Eh? Hey, you've called like
30 times! Are you a stalker?!
Does "Atsumi Kawakami" ring a bell?
I'm her old pal, the coach of the Nikko
Dream Monkeys, Yoko Matsunaga.
Yu Kiyose! We need to talk!
Huh?
Nikko engravings...
Nikko clogs... Jizo statue?!