Mami?
I'm sorry.
Huh?
I... can't join the team.
Huh? Why not?
Um, because after second semester ends,
I'm transferring schools.
Huh?
To think, she'll be gone...
Hey, Sis. Got a sec?
About that ice hockey book you were
looking at... Huh? What's up?
Mami... is leaving!
Huh?
I see.
Mmm.
I can't believe it.
I mean, we've always been together...
I'm so used to her being there,
so when I heard it...
That Mami is leaving...
I thought we'd be together,
even as grown-ups... even as grannys...
I don't want her to go.
I know. But I'm sure Ma feels the same.
Huh?
Do you remember when we
went to the trial class last week?
Hmm?
We all thought it'd just be
something fun to do.
But then, Ma said:
But today, connecting the puck
around was really neat!
For us to work together like that...
It was so much fun!
So... So...!
Let's play ice hockey next week!
By then, she probably knew
she was moving away.
Eh?
Ma rarely speaks up like that.
I think she just wanted to make
more memories with us--
to do more together, while we still can.
Yeah, you're right.
We ought to help her make that possible.
The best thing we can do for Mami is to
send her off with the best memory ever.
Sorry I'm late! I thought of something!
Really?
Let's play a match at
the end of the semester!
A match? Can we handle that?
I had the same idea this morning.
We can try! No, let's do it!
Good idea! There's plenty of time
till the semester ends!
That's more like it!
Huh? A match?
Yup! All of us already talked about it.
Eh?
We heard that you're moving.
Mmm.
Sorry. It felt hard to bring up.
Don't be.
Are you up for the match?
But...
It's getting really fun to play.
We'll ask Saginuma and Takagi
to form a team with us!
Yeah! Okay!
Mmm! Delicious!
Green tea and matcha... Strawberry
sherbet and blueberry yogurt...
Lastly, a mandarine and yuzu citrus combo.
It's the Monkey Complete!
Eat or it's gonna melt.
Leave me alone.
As I was saying, let's play
ice hockey again.
It's so much fun!
Um, about what you said last time...
Hmm?
I didn't know you quit ice hockey 'cuz
I switched to figure skating, Rikorin.
Yeah. 'Cuz I never told you.
Is it true?
Uh-huh. It's not much fun
going all by myself.
If you end up not wanting to play,
I'm not gonna wanna play either.
Huh?
So let's go together!
Fine by me.
I'm sure the other girls
will be there, too!
Saginuma! Takagi!
Hmm?
I knew you'd come!
Hey, we've gotta talk!
Hmm?
Yeah, that's fine. Right, Nao?
I guess so.
Thanks!
Let's start by asking Yoko for help.
Yeah! If she okays it, she can
find a team for us to play!
Sorry to drag you into this,
Saginuma and Takagi.
It's fine! I like the idea, too.
And quit calling me Saginuma.
Rikorin.
Nao.
Okay! Thanks!
I see. I get your reasoning, but...
But?
Does this mean you're all serious
about playing hockey?
Yes!
So in two and a half months,
you want to play a match?
Yes!
Yes, yes, yes!
They're totally into hockey!
You're a bit too happy.
Ahem!
Leave it to me! I'll set it up!
Yay!
That's great!
I hope you're prepared!
Yeah!
Wha--? Can you handle this?
Peace of cake!
Let's start by picking
everyone's position.
First up, goalkeeper--they're a steadfast
player who blocks shots.
Steadfast, huh?
Huh? Me? Really?
In elementary school,
you used to play it in gym.
B-But that was soccer!
Then, Yanagida will play keeper.
With practice, you'll be fine!
Huh? O-Okay! Sure.
Next is center, the crux of the attack.
Gotta be Riko!
Mm-hmm!
Okay! I'll do it!
Next are the wings, who attack
the goal from either side.
How about Manaka and Mami?
Okay! Good with you, Mami?
Yup!
Lastly, the defense. They stop attacks
and connect the puck to the offense.
I'll do that.
Me, too!
Okay, it's settled! Let's get practicing!
It's gonna be tough! I hope you're ready!
Yeah!
Huh?
That's it for now!
Thanks for today...
You guys lack stamina. We need to
address that before anything.
I'll send a training schedule,
so follow it every day.
Okay...
Oh? You regret your decision
after one day?
You're the ones who asked for a match.
I don't regret it!
We're okay.
I regret nothing!
I'm fine.
Ditto.
We'll do our best!
Starting next week,
we'll practice Saturdays, too.
Huh? You didn't even ask me...
Right!
Man, Yoko burst out the gate today.
She's like a whole new person.
It's freaky.
My arms and legs are dead.
Gonna be so sore tomorrow!
But I'm more pumped than ever!
If we're gonna play, let's win!
Yeah! I wanna win!
Agreed. Me, too.
Same.
Yeah! Let's win!
Yeah! Let's do our best!
Yeah!
Oy! That hits the spot!
You sound like a grandpa.
Whatever. Everyone acts old
when they sink in a bath.
That's news to me.
Hold up. Did you say "grandpa"
and not "grandma"?
'Cuz you act like one.
Hey!
Grr!
You get along well.
Been friends since kindergarten.
Really? All of us, too.
Oh, wow.
It's gonna be lonely.
Yeah.
Rikorin, have some delicacy.
Oh, sorry.
We've made lots of memories
together till now,
but I wanna send her off with one
she'll never forget... with ice hockey.
Sis! Soak too long and all
the strawberries will be gone!
Delicious!
Right? They're strawberries from Kao's!
You have a farm?
Yup!
They're even tastier with this!
Must I say it again?
Condensed milk is heresy.
Must I say it again? You're wrong.
Hey! Which do you prefer?
Huh? Um...
Both are good, right?
Yeah.
Won't you stay for dinner?
Huh? Are you sure?
Of course! But make sure
to phone home first.
Okay!
Um! Who do these manga belong to?!
Nao?
Those are Grandma's.
They're from when I was little.
I'm a huge fan of Suzuko Higashio.
Me, too! These are first editions, right?!
And the story collection with her debut!
It's a treasure trove of elusive,
out-of-print classics!
U-Um! Would you let me borrow some?
With pleasure. Help yourself.
O-Oh yeah! Did you read her new one?!
Of course I did!
--It's good!
--Look how much Nao's talking!
Done with inspections.
Good work.
Looking stuff up?
Someone to play those girls.
They're so pumped up, it's pointless
unless it's a decent team.
Sure, but they can't compete
against anyone too strong.
But if they're making memories,
I wanna give 'em a good game.
They've only played for three months.
Is that even possible?
That depends on them.
I'm just setting the stage for 'em.
Good point. Can I lend a hand?
Really? That helps.
At long last, we have an opponent!
Really?!
It's a junior team in Yamanashi.
They're about the same age as you,
but they've been playing
since grade school, so look out!
Still, you've all been training
hard, and it shows.
So, the match is next Sunday.
Give it your best shot, guys!
Right!
It's finally time, huh?
--Yeah.
--I'm getting nervous already.
I barely remember the rules.
I'm giving it my all!
I'm gonna play my heart out!
If Mami's talking like that, I'm pumped!
Yeah!
Since you're all here, um...
Aya, give me a hand?
Hmm? Okay.
Mami, that's...
It's supposed to be a tablecloth, but...
Now we've gotta play our hearts out!
All right! Lez do this!
Now you're sounding like Yoko.
Spare me.
This is a practice match between
Yamanashi Ice Hockey Club
and Dream Monkeys Beginner Team!
Huh? They only have six?
Will they be okay?
Stop staring 'em down.
It feels like we already lost.
Don't worry! We've got the sporty Rikorin
and the steadfast Kao on our team!
Mmm! It's time to show our stuff!
Periods are typically 20 minutes each,
but today's will be 10.
Good luck!
Nice shot!
Sorry.
Don't sweat it! The game's just started!
You guys are playing so stiff!
Play like normal!
Rikorin!
Speed up the transitions!
I know it's your first match and you're
nervous, but you forgot your training.
Don't let the day end in regret.
For these last ten minutes, go all out!
Right!
--Manaka...
--Hmm?
You okay?
Yeah. This is no time to conk out!
Mmm. You're right!
Get it!
Seven to zero.
That's rough.
Yeah.
Sorry, I spaced out.
Don't give up yet.
Right, Mami?
Mmm!
"Don't give up yet."
That's right. Everyone pushed
so hard to get here... for me.
I've gotta return those feelings!
Manaka!
Mami!
It's not over yet!
Mami, you've always been at my side...
We've always been connected,
holding each other's hand...
Nice!
Mami!
Manaka!
So, I'll take this puck
you connected to me...
...and score with it!
Yeah!
Woo-hoo!
--It's in!
--It went in!
Yeah!
Manaka!
Huh?
Good game!
Huh? Wasn't it us who won?
Doesn't feel that way.
That was incredibly fun!
Thank you, everyone!
Yoko, Sato... We barely
just met, but thank you.
Take care.
Keep playing hockey at your new home.
Right.
Where's Mana?
I guess saying goodbye
was too painful for her.
I see.
Mami!
Well, I've gotta go.
Mami...
Till we meet again.
Keep in touch.
Please.
Yeah. Say bye to Mana for me. See you!
Best of luck!
Sis should've been here.
Mami!
Manaka?!
We're always connected,
even when we're apart!
Manaka! I know! I'll never forget that!
Mami!
Manaka!
Thank you, Manaka.
Hey, Atsumi! It's been forever!
You in Kushiro?
Yeah. I'm still here coaching Snow White.
Same story here.
Yoko, I have a favor to ask of you.
See you soon, everyone!