Naomin!
Nice one, Aya!
Riko!
Okay!
Take it, Manami!
Leave it to me!
All you, Mami!
Right! Five seconds left!
It's not over yet!
Yu!
Manaka!
The bonds of our hearts...
...connect the puck!
Yu!
Manaka!
We did it!
Our dream finally came true!
It came true!
C'mon! Time for our Victory Dance!
We are Smile Princess!
Here I am!
You're late, Sis!
Sorry!
The teacher pulled Mana aside.
--Really?
--Mm-hmm!
What'd you do this time, Sis?
Nothing! It was committee stuff!
Today's senbei are good!
Don't talk with your mouth full.
Want tea?
Sure do!
--Here.
--Thanks!
--Gather up!
--Right!
Mmm! Nothing says springtime
of youth like sweat and sports!
Our embroidery club counts, too!
Of course! It's existed
since Grandma's time!
Stitch by stitch, we've made
masterpieces across generations!
We all share a common thread!
Hot!
Yeah, yeah. As president of such a
time-honored club, quit talking and work.
Aya, let her drink tea in peace.
You're too easy on her, Kao!
Hurry up!
Yeah, yeah.
Now then...
Oh! It's a tough one today!
But that's what makes it
fulfilling when you finish!
It's such a sense of accomplishment!
Yeah, yeah! You've got that right!
Hey! Move your hands!
Hold up. I'm image training.
For embroidery?
It's very important.
That's my Mami! You get it!
Jeez! Stop humoring her, Mami!
All done!
At last!
That was hard today!
Whoa! It's so pretty! That's Mami for you!
Thanks.
In comparison, yours looks crude!
It's called being bold!
Yours doesn't even match the pattern!
It's called being unique!
What a neat color choice!
Right?!
You're giddy when Mami praises you.
What's wrong with that?!
That's all for today! Thanks for coming!
Thanks, everyone!
Wanna come over?
--Yeah!
--Of course!
We're home!
Pardon us!
Welcome home!
Um, there's a stitch I kinda need
help with.
Can you help me later?
Of course!
Well, let's do our thing!
Ah! Soakin' it in!
An open-air bath whenever we want!
It's the perks of being friends!
Oh, hey! They wanna film at our ryokan!
What?! Awesome!
For a drama? A movie?!
A variety show, or something!
Really? That's cool!
Huh? What do you mean by, "or something"?
Mom got so excited by the call,
she can't even remember.
Huh? For real?
But they're mailing the details.
Hey, do you think it's a TV
special about you guys?!
--Eh?!
--Huh?!
"Cute Next-Gen Hostesses
of an Age-Old Ryokan."
Or, "Newbie Hostesses at Work."
Those sorta shows are trending!
--They sure are!
--Right?
Yeah? You think?
Make sure we're here for it!
For "Cute Hostesses and Their
Support Crew," or something?
You just wanted to say "cute hostesses."
Secret's out?
Still, the producer must have
a good eye to pick our ryokan.
Spouting more self-praise?
I "sing" my own praises.
Strawberries from Yanagida
Farms are the best!
So juicy!
And super sweet!
I could eat a million!
Thanks. My dad would be
happy to hear you say that.
Sis! Stop chowing 'em down!
It's okay! They're good!
That's no excuse!
You're the one dousing 'em
in condensed milk!
It overpowers the strawberry!
Grr! The milk elevates
the strawberry taste!
How do you like ramen?
Salty!
And curry?
Sweet!
In perfect sync.
Right? How about strawberries?
Eat 'em plain!
With condensed milk!
That's where they differ.
Very curious.
Tasty!
You're a heretic.
Oh! I forgot!
Hmm?
I was late today 'cuz I got asked to
put something on the bulletin board!
This!
Ice hockey hands-on trial class?
Nikko's pro team, the Dream Monkeys,
is putting it on this Sunday!
Yeah?
And what about it?
Let's try it out!
You two can skate, right?
We did it in gym class.
Yeah.
Well...
Doesn't it sound cool?!
It might be worth trying out, I guess.
Ice hockey, huh? That sounds pretty scary.
Won't we get hurt?
It's fine! It'll be an experience!
C'mon, let's all go!
Grandma always says,
"Try new experiences!"
Hmm. I doubt she meant ice hockey by that.
Still, it might be fun to try!
Yeah, it's worth a shot!
I'm up for trying it once!
Right?! Let's do it, Mami!
Let's all go together!
Mmm! I'll give it a go!
Great! That settles it! I'll apply for us!
That's it. Once you wrap the thread, use
your left hand to pull and right to push.
Yes! Well done!
Ah, so that's how you do it!
All right! Thanks, Grandma!
Of course. You're so
passionate about learning.
Well, there's a project I'm trying to
finish before second semester ends.
I see.
But don't focus too hard
or your eyes will go bad.
Got it!
Revolution!
Aww! Anything but that!
Don't underestimate the Poor!
Ugh! Let's play again!
All right! One more time!
I haven't been here
since our gym field trip!
When does ice hockey season start?
Sorry!
We're a little late!
'Cuz Ayaka overslept!
Nuh-uh! You wouldn't get up
so I fell asleep!
Enough excuses! C'mon, let's go!
It's this way.
Eh?!
Listen up! Let's start
this season with spirit!
Be kind! Make 'em think:
"I wanna come back next week!"
Right!
It starts with: "Ice hockey is kinda fun!"
And then: "Maybe I'll go next week!"
Soon enough: "Maybe I'll join the
Dream Monkeys!"
Can't you see?!
Right!
Understand?! You need to be super nice!
--This is what you've been training for!
--Um, Yoko?
What, Sato?!
You're making a face
that'll scare 'em away.
For real?
Ew! I've got wrinkles here?! Since when?!
That's your issue? Huh?
Yoko, they're coming!
What?! Sato, put it on!
R-Right!
Refreshing!
Sure feels good!
Are you here for the trial class?!
Y-Yeah!
Welcome to Kirifuri Arena!
My, you're all so cute!
Let's see. Kinugawa Junior High
3rd year, Manaka Mizusawa,
Kaoruko Yanagida, Mami Ono,
and 2nd year, Ayaka Mizusawa, right?
Yup!
Thanks for coming to the ice hockey trial class!
Let's head on in!
Okay!
--Brr!
--It's chilly!
I'm excited!
Me, too!
Change into your gym clothes.
Roger that!
Huh?
Um, are you guys participating
in the trial class, too?
Yeah, that's right.
So are we!
I'm Manaka Mizusawa,
a 3rd year at Kinugawa.
I'm Riko Saginuma from Kirifuri.
And here's my extra, Naomi Takagi.
We're 3rd years, too.
Don't call me an extra.
Nice to meet you!
You, too!
Nice! It's all girls this year!
And what a harvest at that!
In junior high, though.
That's fine! It's an early harvest!
At last, my ambition will come to light!
You mean, that one idea of mixing
ice hockey and entertainment?
Yes! First, I'll train the girls to play
like proper Dream Monkeys!
But after each win, they'll do
a victory dance on the ice!
Such a clever performance
will delight the audience!
It'll bring in people who never
had interest in ice hockey!
Then I'll appear in my old uniform
and sing a song while I'm at it!
We'll attract the biggest
crowds you've ever seen!
That's my ambition!
More like your delusion.
You're saying some pretty crazy things.
Got a problem?!
No!
Anyway, don't you dare
let these girls slip away!
Right!
Now then, we'll start with warm-ups
to help prevent injuries.
We'll stretch along to a rhythm.
Ice hockey uses a lot of muscles.
We'll do upper body first.
--One, two, three, four,
--Interesting stretch!
five, six, seven, eight.
--It sure is!
Two, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Here's one more useful for games. Ready?
One, two, three, four
five, six, seven, eight.
--This clearly isn't a stretch.
--Two, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
It's more like a step.
No, this isn't a step!
It's a dance
used to evade defenders!
--She said "dance" clear as day.
--Four, five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four
--Yeah.
--This is fun!
five, six, seven, eight.
Everyone's keeping up, right?
On to the next dance routine!
Dance routine?
You're doing great!
Now that you've
warmed up, let's get you on the rink.
You can change into
your uniforms
this way.
Okay!
At last!
I can't wait!
--Yeah. (comment)
--We get to wear uniforms!
These girls...
This could work!
I wonder what that phony
stretch dance thing was about.
If it went any longer, I would've left.
Hey now. The fun's about to start.
Whoa!
It looks like a robot!
Wow. It's lighter than I thought.
We can move easy in these.
Yeah!
It seems like so much.
If someone
runs into you, won't it hurt?
It's okay. In girls' hockey, body checking
is an illegal hit.
It shouldn't happen.
I see!
I feel stoked!
I feel like a pilot.
All right, guys!
The trial class
starts now!
Let's rock and roll!
"Rock and roll"?
Is it safe to say everyone can skate?
Yeah!
Okay! That's the locals for you.
Try to keep up with me!
It's weird skating in gear.
You okay, Ayaka?
Yeah!
Next up is edge control!
Control it! Go slow if needed!
Now then, you've warmed up to the rink
so let's talk about the basics.
Games last for 60 minutes,
broken into three, 20-minute periods.
Two teams compete to score
the most goals in that time.
There're two pieces of
equipment you need to play.
The first is a puck.
You score
by hitting it in the goal.
It's about as big as a jingoro senbei...
It's made of black rubber
and is very hard.
You'll be sorry if it
hits you, so be careful.
Ugh. I don't wanna get hurt.
Yoko, what are you scaring 'em for?
And this is a hockey stick.
It's like a bath-stirring stick.
You use the stick to control
the puck by moving it like this.
Now, you guys try it out!
This is hard!
I can't do it!
It's okay. Nobody's good at first.
Everyone get in a circle
and practice passing!
Whoops! Sorry!
Mizusawa!
I got it!
Here it comes, Mami!
Okay!
One, two...!
Nice stop, Mami!
Huh? Uh, yeah!
You guys did great today!
Thank you!
What do you think of hockey?
I was rusty since I haven't skated
in a while, but it came back to me!
I'm new to using a stick,
but it was kinda fun!
Mm-hmm!
I see!
I'm sad we couldn't play more.
What she said.
Can I count on you to show up next week?!
Okay!
I was hoping for "okey-dokey."
You're so old-fashioned, Yoko.
I'm glad you all had fun!
Be careful heading home!
Okay!
Whew! That was so much fun!
The hours just flew by!
I know! It was over before I knew it!
What a fun experience!
I had a blast!
Think you'll come back?
Maybe!
Um...!
Hmm?
Well...
Ice hockey was fun!
Passing the puck around...
Everyone chasing after it...
Yeah.
I love embroidery.
Stitch by stitch,
watching a project come together...
There's such a sense of accomplishment!
Mami?
But today, connecting the puck
around was really neat!
For us to work together like that...
It was so much fun!
So... So...!
Let's play ice hockey next week!
Mami...
I'm surprised you're the one saying it.
Agreed.
Yeah, let's! Let's do it!
Let's do it again next week, too!
Okey-dokey!
Right?
Yup!
Old-fashioned!
In that moment, I--no, we...
discovered
our sparkling springtime of youth!
Connect the puck, even in a game!